astrology-online.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for Astrology Online 

**Astrology Online** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Astrology Online ](http://www.astrology-online.com/)

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. _Our advertisers set cookies to prevent the same ad from always appearing._ **Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your users’ browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on your website.**

Please refer to your browser's options to learn more about cookies and how to disable them.

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the order forms is used for other purposes. _We use the information you submit only to fill your order._

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
_Demographic information is required to do astrology reports._

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Astrology Online** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Children's Guidelines 

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent 
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
